Think about yourself in a relationship.
If your man's not talking to you, not giving you hugs, or whoever you are.
I don't think everybody's with a man, right?
But if your partner is not being good to you, how do you feel about that relationship?
And how do you respond?
You're in a relationship with your body.
And if you're not doing your part in showing up as a good partner, don't expect a good outcome.
Oof.
No, that's real.
I don't think we think about it enough that way.
We don't.
A lot of us are treating our bodies like a side piece.
Hey, girl.
I'm going to get to you when I get to you.
And my man over here, my life, is more important.
And that's what happens is that we don't get to our bodies until we get to them.
And usually that's when they done pulled up outside the house making all this noise.
Listen, spray paint in your car, kicking in your windows.